<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Harshad</title>
    <link>http://harshad.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Harshad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://harshad.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Org mode and orgzly</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/org-and-orgzly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/org-and-orgzly/</guid>
      <description>When I first heard of org-mode, I thought org-mode, like any other task management app, would just work out of the box and be my task management planner inside emacs. But, I was so wrong. Org-mode is so much more than that. Instead of thinking of org-mode as a &amp;#34;plug-and-play task management software&amp;#34;, one should think of org mode as a toolset for building their own personal knowledge management system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pin</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/pin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/pin/</guid>
      <description>Anyone who works in a field related to computer software, ends up running a bunch of CLI (command line interface) commands pretty often. The longer you stay in the field, the larger is your command set. With new systems being invented everyday, the complexity of commands being run is also increasing. Day by day, I am finding myself running more and more complex commands. That&amp;#39;s when I decided I need something to manage these commands for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick emacs&#43;cscope hack for broken symlinks</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/quick-cscope-emacs-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/quick-cscope-emacs-hack/</guid>
      <description>I use cscope in emacs as my primary code browsing tool for Linux kernel development. However, I started to get annoyed by cscope errors for broken symlinks. What is happening is that during the Linux kernel build process, a few symlinks get created which are not needed once the kernel is built. I presume that the build tooling doesn&amp;#39;t clean up these symlinks after they are removed and that confuses the cscope program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Website with Password Protection</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/static-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/static-website/</guid>
      <description>After numerous attempts at finding a cheap and easy solution to making a password protected static website, I finally have settled my mind on one! Before going over the solution let me go over the requirements that I had in my mind for the website:
Cheap Static and blog-aware Password protection on a part of the website Smooth and easy workflow to move content from private part to public Preferably, an automatic CI/CD I tried multiple solutions such as setting up Heroku dynos, CloudCanon etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizing Song chords</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/writing-music-chords/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/writing-music-chords/</guid>
      <description>I often struggled to keep chords for songs I played in a handy place. For a couple of years I have been maintaining chords in a Google Doc. Given the forgetful person that I&amp;#39;m, storing all the chords in one place has come as a blessing. Having all the chords in one place has helped me to be more organized about my music. It has helped me collaborate better with other musicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dil Mein Jaagi</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/dil-mein-jagi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/dil-mein-jagi/</guid>
      <description>Dil mein jaagi is a beautiful composition by Amit Trivedi. Check out the original song here. However, it has been highly under noticed. My wife Rithisha (who is an amazing singer() btw) and I decided to give this song a shot. What started as just a jam back in 2016 summer, ended up becoming a full fledged performance. All thanks to Rithisha, Shardul, Rucha and Vaishnavh for their amazing contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rehna Tu</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/rehna-tu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/rehna-tu/</guid>
      <description> Rehna Tu is originally a song from movie Delhi 6. We interpreted it very differently and here&amp;#39;s our take on it.
Links to this note </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yaava Mohana</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/yaava-mohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/yaava-mohana/</guid>
      <description> This is a really beautiful Kannada composition! I fell in love with it the first time I heard it. Do listen :)
Links to this note </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Website Index Page</title>
      <link>http://harshad.me/posts/old-github-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harshad.me/posts/old-github-index/</guid>
      <description>I am a Graduate Student at Carnegie Mellon University. My main research interests are Networks, Internet Architecture, CCN; also I am interested in Storage, Operating Systems. Recently, I have have started loving Probability. Thanks to Prof. Mor Harchol-Balter. Advised by Prof. Peter Steenkiste, I work on a future internet architecture project called eXpressive Internet Architecture(XIA) at Carnegie Mellon.
Before CMU Before coming to Carnegie Mellon, I was working as a device driver developer at AirTight Networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
